Welcome back to the new blog and a few
days ago I had given you an update that
Vaibhav Bhai had met with an accident, so
if you guys have seen the video, then we
went with him to the agency but nothing had happened there yet,
after that, the next day
Vaibhav Bhai went alone, so how did he get the further
procedure done, so
brother tell me what all things were there,
what all papers were there and what
details were you asked for there, brother, the
vehicle was already damaged a lot, let me
show you the bike first, so here is the
bike and it has been completely changed,
where this headlight of mine was very
much worn out, it was worn out so much, exactly
about 1 inch, it has been
completely changed and this column of the headlight was
also scratched a
little here
and this has become a mark of ours, it is
not accidental, but I will change it
sometime later and this indicator of ours was
damaged, I have a photo of it
and here
we will show you later how the bike is
What all damages had come in it and this
brake lever of mine was damaged, the
entire brake mechanism here was damaged in
effect and this side mirror of mine which is the rear
view mirror was also damaged, the
company has installed a new one from the back and if we
look at the rest, my leg guard of the bike,
this leg guard of mine was bent backwards
and there were scratches in it too, so the company has
changed it completely, this will
also be completely changed, there is some other damage somewhere in the bike
and I had forgotten this silencer, the
rings covering of the silencer have also been
changed and along with it, there was just this much
damage, there was damage in it, the
company has installed a new one for me and
given it in the claim and this meter
column of ours, meter column as we call it,
this meter column of mine was also broken, there was
no impact on it completely, the
impact on it will
break it completely and this meter had also damaged our meter,
from here our meter was
looking absolutely fine but when we were turning it
off, it got damaged  The meter was showing on time,
although I did not see it like that, but the
company, after seeing this, called me and said
that sir, there is a problem in your meter as well, so
I said there was no issue in the meter, so
I thought that there could have been something
somewhere else, the
service was very good, the rest of the car was
given to me after a complete wash and
everything was found in good condition,
I will tell you the details of what all is installed in the flame,
my
DL and Aadhar card, PAN card and
RC of the car and my insurance paper were installed, so so many
things were installed and I
want to ask that in how many days your
bike has been repaired, my bike has been repaired
in 17 days, I have to wait for the bike for 17 days
and
I had also created a little pressure
on Bhaiya, the manager of the service center,
however, he said that Bhaiya,
according to the things that have been changed, you have got the
bike very quickly, friend, let us see
because the bike itself is
not available, the
showroom parts are being made,
even the car itself is not available  It is available,
its
microphone is good, the
rate is also quite right.
I also got a minor injury
in my hand, that's all, there was no
problem in getting the claim and the
support in the rest of the claim has been very good.
Every time I have called the service center, I was happy with it. I would
not like to send them by calling them workers, the employees there were
very nice, they
talked to me very well, even
before the manager, the workers there or you
can say the employees there
dealt with me and solved all my problems. Did
you face any issue in the process? Did you face any issue?
I was in
constant touch with the
manager there and the employee there
who works in car service also
supported me a lot, he gave me his
number also, he said brother if you have
any issue then tell me, I
told him everything and my car's lineman was
also out, sorry friends sir, the center was out,
he was also out, so its  Because of this, I started having
problems in handling as well, so
I also told the service there that
I am also having problems in handling, so that needs to be
looked into, which is not visible but happens, so
in the end I want to ask that after
claiming everything, after completing all the procedures, what is the total
charge that you have incurred,
your friends, if you look at it, my
total cost for getting this car
repaired was absolutely zero
because I had zero depth in it,
my complete insurance has not been done yet,
this is in the last of October, at the very end of the
month of October, I have the
car and it has been almost
3 months since I
started the car and this is in January, on 9th
January, I had an accident and I
received the bike on 20th January,
I was called and said that sir please
come and take your bike and I took my bike
and it became absolutely brand new and the
total expense incurred in it was close to  It is
₹1000. He understood from me that I had a
lot of need for the vehicle and I was also in
great need and was facing a lot of problems,
so I
requested Bhaiya and the manager
he said that sir you can do this, there is an
amount, he told me that
friend it has taken about 200 rupees to come
because when it gets completely cleared
then I have not been charged for the due amount yet,
he collected thousand rupees from me just now
and now he said that when the due amount is received then
if it is less then the remaining money will be
returned to me, so I mean
your charge has come below ₹1000, thousand
rupees
only on Monday, hence ₹1000 can also be
returned, so what I
mean is that I can take the remaining money from there,
and you can see the
bike brother, and this number plate, it is a
part of RTO, everything else will be the vehicle,
only that changes, it comes inside the RTO, so
your number plate will
not change, you will have to get it refunded separately.  You will have to get it installed and
come after paying the money, so the rest was something like this, I have posted the review and claim in the
same way here, you
bike and I did not spend much, it was only
₹1000 and maybe it is even
less than that,
for more details you can also comment
in Adarsh's comment section below and if all
your problems are like this,
if you want to claim on bike,
how to get it, what documents are required,
we mention that also in the description below, then
we will give you all the details,
because both me and Adarsh ​​are
supporting this channel together, although this
channel is Adarsh, I also support it, so
I will try, I will make sure that
whatever documents you have required are mentioned in the description description
and
I will get all these things mentioned there, together we have
given you all the details as to
what will be required in the claim and what will not be required and
how will the vehicle be repaired, in how many days will it be repaired,
what will be the charge and further we
end the video here, I am serious
In the next few days, people say bye-bye.